# TYSON COTTAIN

## UX / UI DESIGNER

#### DETAILS

Portfolio — tysoncottam.com

Phone — 801.822.9198

Email — tysoncottam@gmail.com

# SKILLS

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Figma

Invision

HTML 5

SCSS

SASS

## VOLUNTEER

Missionary —
The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints
(Sept 2013 - Sept 2015)

### **PROFILE**

I strive to create a premium user experience. My designs are intuitive, modern, and intelligent. Interacting with a product should create a positive influence on the consumer and drive them to share it with others. I enjoy helping clients create the perfect experience for their audience.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Utah Valley University**

Orem, UT

Fall 2022

Pursuing Bachelor Degree: Interaction Design

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Instructure

Pleasant Grove, UT

L1 Support Engineer

June 2018 - Present

- Consistently maintaining above 90% CSAT each month with 35 cases daily
- Resolving client's concerns within the first contact
- Organizing important case details to provide clear instructions to client through follow up emails
- Communicating with co-workers on problems they are facing and providing detailed instructions for solutions.

#### **Advanced Conservator Resources**

Draper, UT

Accounting Consultant

Mar 2017 - June 2018

- Electronically organized over 10,000 client records such as financial documents, checks, and legal statements
- Performed accounting verification on client bank reconciliation statements to ensure accurate financial statements for the Department of Veteran's Affairs
- Enhanced numerous business processes to ensure proper compliance for sensitive customer data

#### DownEast Home

South Jordan, UT

Warehouse Manager

Feb 2016 - Mar 2017

- Received shipments and ensured quality product control for over 1,000 shipments
- Excelled in managing customer expectations and providing a high level of customer satisfaction on a daily basis
- Managed excel spreadsheet to ensure inventory control